This program is built around projects.
这门课程以项目为基础
When you complete each project,
当你完成每个项目后
you'll submitted to one of our expert reviewers who will give you personalized feedback.
你需要向我们的审阅专家提交项目 对方会提供个性化反馈
This project will help you gain valuable experience and
这些项目可以帮助你掌握宝贵的经验
build a portfolio that you can share with potential employers.
并构建可以展示给潜在雇主的作品集
The first project is available at the start of the program.
第一个项目位于课程的开端部分
In this product, you use Pandas and NumPy to
在此项目中 你将使用 Pandas 和 NumPy
analyze a real dataset of passengers on the Titanic.
分析泰坦尼克号乘客这一真实数据集
And based on this information,
然后根据这些信息
you'll be able to predict their survival.
预测他们的存活情况
To heighten your understanding,
为了加强理解
and training, and testing machine learning models,
并训练和测试机器学习模型
you will use scikit-learn and regression to
你将使用 scikit learn 和回归算法
analyze the real data setup housing prices in Boston.
分析波士顿的实际房价数据集
You'll build and optimize a model to predict prices of housing.
你将构建并优化预测房价的模型
In the supervised learning project,
在监督学习项目中
your task will be to build a classification model to
你的任务是构建一个分类模型
identify the best potential donors for a charity.
并用该模型帮助慈善机构发现最有可能捐款的潜在捐助者
You'll be able to use several classification algorithms and optimize them for quality.
你将能够使用多个分类算法并通过改善它们提高质量
In the unsupervised learning project,
在非监督学习的实战项目中
you will study a real dataset of customers of a company.
你将研究某个公司的实际客户数据集
And you'll apply several and supervised learning techniques
你将应用多个非监督学习技巧
in order to extract valuable information from the data.
从数据中提取宝贵的信息
After you've gain expertise on the core algorithms of machine learning,
在掌握机器学习核心算法技巧后
you'll be working on projects to strengthen
你将通过完成实战项目
your understanding of deep and reinforcement learning.
加强对深度强化学习的理解
The deep learning project will have a bill to
在深度学习的项目中
convolutional neural network to recognize dung breeds from images.
你将构建一个卷积神经网络 从图片中识别狗类品种
Furthermore, if an image of a human is provided,
此外 如果提供的是人类图片
the algorithm will guess which breed of dog looks the most like that human.
该算法将猜测哪种狗类品种看起来最像此人
You'll also be able to improve your sales significantly by using pretrain networks.
你还将能够通过使用预先训练的网络显著改善效率
You'll then use deep reinforcement learning to design
然后 你将使用深度强化学习
a simulated quadcopter that learns to take off hover and land all by itself.
设计一个学会自己起飞并降落的模拟四轴飞行器
As a bonus, you will be able to integrate these behaviors into
在加分项目中 你将能够将这些行为整合到一个无人飞行器系统中
a single endoin system that can autonomously fly from point A to Point B.
该飞行器能自主地从 A 处飞行到 B 处
Finally, in your capsule project,
最后 在毕业项目中
you'll be able to distinguish yourself by building a machine learning project to solve
你将构建一个机器学习项目来解决你感兴趣的问题
a problem that you are passionate about using any dataset of your choice.
并使用任何数据集 从而展现自己的个人技能
Our network of advisory reviewers will guide you through your proposal
我们的审阅专家将在此过程中为你提供指导
face and will give you solid feedback on your model,
并为你的模型 数据和流程
your data, and your procedure.
提供具体的反馈
With these projects under your wings,
完成这些项目后
you'll have both the skills and
你将不仅掌握了这些技能
the portfolio to become a successful machine learning engineer.
而且拥有可以展示的作品集 最终成为一名成功的机器学习工程师
We can't wait to see your contribution to
我们迫不及待地想要看到你通过应用机器学习技术
the advancement of technology through machine learning.
对科技发展带来的贡献了！